<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Products>
  <Product>

    <ID>1</ID>
    <Title>Biryani</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Biryani.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Biryani.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Meat is flavoured with herbs, spices and seasoning and cooked along with aromatic basmati rice to prepare one of Indian’s finest foods, the Biryani. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Take 500g of chicken, entire contents of this packet, 100g of plain yoghurt and 300ml of water in a cooking pan. Mix well.

2. Cover with a lid and cook on a low heat for 20 minutes.

3. Cook 300g of Basmati rice separately. (Rice recipe is given below).

4. Spread the cooked rice on the cooked chicken in an even layer. Add cashew nuts, raisins and 2 tbsp. Of pure ghee (clarified butter)to it.

5. Cover and let it cook on steam for 10 minutes, on a low heat.

Lamb. Take 500g of lamb, entire contents of this packet, 100g of plain yoghurt and 450ml of water in a cooking pan. Mix well. Cover with a lid and simmer for about 60 minutes on a low heat. Follow the rest of the recipe as above.

Vegetable. Take 500g of vegetables, entire contents of this packet, 50g of plain of plain yoghurt and 450ml of water in a cooking pan. Mix well. Cover with a lid and simmer for about 20 minutes on a low heat. Follow the rest of the recipe as above.

Rice. Wash 300g of basmati rice. Add 4 ½ cups (675ml) of water, 1 ½ tsp. of salt, 1 tea spoon. of sugar and 1 table spoon of oil to the rice. Mix it well and cook until all the water has evaporated.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (25%), Refined Sunflower Oil (13%), Coriander Leaves (9%), Garlic (12%), Ginger (12%), Sugar, Salt, Mint Leaves, Green Chilli, Coriander, Fennel, Tomato, Spices, Red Chilli Powder, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Title>Butter Chicken</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Butter-Chicken.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Butter-Chicken.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>The best known chicken dish from the land of Punjab, served in a rich creamy sauce delicately flavoured with nutmeg and saffron. Mild in taste, best served with ‘tandoori rotis’ or naan bread. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails> 

1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 225ml. Of water in a bowl to form a smooth.

2. Saute 250g of boneless chicken (small pieces) in 15g of butter on a medium heat till it turns golden brown.

3. Add the mixture from the bowl and simmer on a low heat for about 10 minutes, until the sauce becomes thick.

4. Add 50g of fresh single or double cream and bring to a boil.
</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (35%), Refined Sunflower Oil (18%), Coriander Leaves (12%), Garlic (8%), Ginger (8%), Sugar, Salt, Tomato, Spices, Red Chilli Powder, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <Title>Chicken Achari</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chicken-Achari.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chicken-Achari.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Chicken in a tangy mixture, flavoured with traditional pickle spices.</Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 2 teas spoons of lemon juice (half a lemon) and 6 or 7 table spoons (100g) of plain yoghurt in a bowl to form a smooth.

2. Apply this mixture to 500g of boneless chicken (small pieces).

3. In a non-stick cooking pan, sauté the above mixture in 1 table spoon (15g) of butter on a medium heat for about 15 minutes until the chicken is tender.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Refined Sunflower Oil (20%), Coriander Leaves (15%), Garlic (8%), Ginger (8%), Iodized salt, Green Chilli, Spices and Condiments, Turmeric
</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <Title>Chicken Capsicum and Onion</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chicken-Capsicum-and-Onion.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chicken-Capsicum-and-Onion.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Chicken in a tangy, sweet and sour masala.</Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 6 or 7 table spoons (100g) of plain yoghurt in a bowl to form a smooth mixture.

2. Apply this mixture to 500g of boneless chicken (small pieces) and saute on a medium heat for about 15 minutes until the chicken is tender.

3. In a cooking pan, saute 3 medium (150g) capsicums and 3 medium (200g) onions (both cut into dices) in 1 table spoon (15g) of butter on a medium heat for 2 minutes.

4. Add 6 or 7 table spons (100g) of tomato ketchup and stir well. Add the cooked chicken to this, stir and serve.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Garlic (20%), Ginger (20%), Refined Sunflower Oil (15%), Red Chilli Powder (10%), Salt, Spices, Sugar, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <Title>Chicken Curry</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chicken-Curry.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chicken-Curry.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>A deliciously thick yoghurt, green chilli and coriander based curry as preferred by the Persian rulers who established the Moghul rule in India.</Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Take 500g of chicken, entire contents of this packet, 100g of plain yoghurt and 225ml of water in a cooking pan.

2. Mix it well and cook on a medium heat for about 20 minutes until the chicken is tender.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (40%), Refined Sunflower Oil (16%), Coriander Leaves (9%), Garlic (12%), Ginger, Salt, Spices, Green Chilli, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <Title>Chicken Karahi</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chicken-Karahi.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chicken-Karahi.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>This rich sauce has succulent, pieces of chicken with a piquant taste. The sauce is deliciously thick with capsicum and onion. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails></CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (42%), Refined Sunflower Oil (13%), Garlic (9.5%), Ginger (9.5%), Coriander Leaves (8%), Mint Leaves (5.5%), Salt (5%), Spices (3.5%), Tomato (3%), Turmeric (1%)</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <Title>Chicken Madras</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chicken-Madras.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chicken-Madras.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>A rich hot sauce flavoured with aromatic spices and a hint of coconut from the land of madras. Best served with naan bread. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Mix the entire contents of this packet with 350ml of water in a cooking pan.

2. Add 300 to 400g of chicken pieces. Simmer on a medium heat for about 20 minutes until the chicken is tender and the sauce become thick.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (31%), Refined Sunflower Oil (13.5%), Desiccated Coconut (8%), Coriander Leaves (8%), Garlic (7.5%), Ginger (7.5%), Salt (7.5%), Green Chilli, Coriander, Spices, Tamarind, Red Chilli Powder, Turmeric</Ingredients>
   <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <Title>Chicken Tikka Masala</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chicken-Tikka-Masala.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chicken-Tikka-Masala.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>A mild chicken dish in a rich aromatic tomato based sauce,with a hint of mint and coriander. Best served with naan bread or aromatic basmati rice. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 300ml.of water and 100g of plain yoghurt in a bowl to form a smooth mixture.

2. Saute 2250g of boneless chicken (small pieces) in 15g of butter on a medium heat till it turns golden brown.

3. Add the mixture from the bowl and simmer on a low heat for about 10 minutes.

4. Add 50g of fresh single or double cream and bring to a boil.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (29%), Refined Sunflower oil (14%), Coriander Leaves (12.5%), Garlic (9%), Ginger (9%), Tomato (8%), Salt, Spices, Red chilli Powder, Green Chilli, Turmeric</Ingredients>
     <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <Title>Chickpeas Curry</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chickpeas-Curry.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chickpeas-Curry.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>From the land of Punjab, India, this chickpea curry is seasoned with tamarind and a hint of sugar. This dish is best served with Chappati’s and Plain yoghurt. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Take 200g can of chickpeas, entire contents of this packet and 450ml of water in a cooking pan.

2. Mix it well and simmer on a medium heat, stirring occasionally, for 10 minutes until the chickpeas turn soft.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (35%), Refined Sunflower Oil (17.5%), Coriander Leaves (9%), Garlic (7%), Spices (8%), Ginger (4.5%), Tomato, Salt
, Sugar, Tamarind, Green Chilli, Raw Mango Powder, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>10</ID>
    <Title>Chutney Chicken</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Chutney-Chicken.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Chutney-Chicken.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Chicken cooked to perfection in a thick mixture of Indian spices and green herbs. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 3 table spoons (50g) of plain yoghurt and 3 table spoons of water in a bowl to form a smooth mixture.

2. In a cooking pan, sauté 250g of boneless chicken (small pieces) in 1 table spoon (15g) of butter on a medium flame till it turns golden brown (5 to 6 minutes).

3. Add the mixture from the bowl, stir and simmer on a low flame for about 2 to 3 minutes until the chicken is tender.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (10%), Refined Sunflower Oil (15%), Coriander Leaves (14%), Garlic (20%), Ginger, Salt, Mint Leaves, Green Chilli (8%), Spices and Condiments, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>11</ID>
    <Title>Fish Fry</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/fish-fry.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/fish-fry.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Fresh fish in a mixture of Indian spices and green herbs, shallow fried to perfection. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 2 table spoons of white vinegar and 2 table spoons of water in a bowl to form a smooth mixture.

2. Apply this mixture to 350g – 400g of fish slices of your choice.

3. Heat 2 tea spoons of oil in a non-stick frying pan. Place the fish slices and cook on a low heat for 4-5 minutes.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Refined Sunflower Oil (8%), Coriander Leaves (15%), Garlic (25%), Ginger (6%), Salt, Mint Leaves, Green Chilli (10%), Spices and Condiments, Tamarind, Turmeric</Ingredients>
   <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>12</ID>
    <Title>Goan Fish Curry</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Goan-Fish-Curry.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Goan-Fish-Curry.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Goa – best known for its beautiful beatches and exotic cuisine, brings this popular local dish. A rich coconut based sauce fused with assorted spices from this region of India.</Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 300ml of water and 150ml of thick coconut milk in a cooking pan.

2. Cook the mixture on a medium heat and bring to a boil. Add 400g to 500g of fish of your choice (cut into slices).

3. Simmer on a low heat for about 5 to 7minutes, till the fish is completely done.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (41%), Refined Sunflower Oil (10.5%), Desiccated Coconut (9.5%), Coriander Leaves (9%), Garlic, Ginger, Salt (6.5%), Spices, Red Chilli Powder, Tamarind, Coriander Seeds, Turmeric</Ingredients>
   <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>13</ID>
    <Title>Lamb Curry</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Lamb-Curry.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Lamb-Curry.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Tender pieces of lamb flaovered with herbs, spices and seasoning and best served witharomatic basmati rice or naan bread to make one of India’s finest and favourite dishes. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 900ml 0f water in a cooking pan.

2. Add 500g of lamb pieces and stir well.

3. Cover with a lid and simmer on a medium heat for about 60 minutes until the lamb is tender.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (39%), Refined Sunflower Oil (14.5%), Coriander Leaves (8%), Garlic (8.5%), Ginger (8.5%), Salt, Mint Leaves, Green Chilli, Coriander, Spices, Red Chilli Powder, Tomato, Turmeric</Ingredients>
   <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>14</ID>
    <Title>Rogan Josh</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Rogan-Josh.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Rogan-Josh.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Brought to India by the mughal empire, adapted in India in Kashmir. Onions and tomatoes tone down this fiery sounding culinary delight.</Description>
    <Price>2.99€</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 750ml. Of hot water in a bowl to form a smooth

2. In frying pan, Saute 500g of lamb in tspb. of oil on a medium heat, until the excess water evaporates and the lamb starts it turning golden brown.

3. Add the mixture from the bowl and simmer on a low heat until the sauce becomes thick and the lamb is tender.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (45%), Refined Sunflower Oil (14%), Coriander Leaves (10%), Garlic (8%), Ginger, Salt, Tomato, Spices, Red Chilli Powder, Green Chilli, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>15</ID>
    <Title>Tandoori Chicken</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Tandoori-Chicken.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Tandoori-Chicken.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>This dish is named after the Indian Tandoor, a clay oven in which the meat is cooked after it has been marinated in yoghurt and spices. Now not only a favourite in India, but across the globe.</Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Take entire of this packet and 100g of plain yoghurt in a bowl. Mix it well.

2. Apply this mixture to 1kg of chicken and grill it on a medium heat, turning regularly until the chicken is cooked.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Refined Sunflower Oil (13%), Garlic (32%), Ginger (20%), Salt (17.5%), Spices (14.5%), Red chilli powder, Turmeric</Ingredients>
    <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>16</ID>
    <Title>Vindaloo</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Vindaloo.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Vindaloo.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>Not for the faint hearted. Cooked in a rich sauce consisting of assorted chillies from all over India. Best served with naan bread and a cold drink.</Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. Apply 2 table spoons of vinegar to 500g of lamb and marinate for 30 minutes.

2. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 750ml of hot water in a bowl to form a smooth.

3. After marination, sauté the lamb on a medium heat, in a frying pan, until the excess water evaporates and the lamb starts turning golden brown.

4. Add the mixture from the bowl and simmer on a low heat until the sauce becomes thick and the lamb is tender.

</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (36%), Refined Sunflower Oil (13%), Coriander Leaves (7.5%), Tomato (8%), Garlic, Ginger, Salt, Green Chilli, Spices, Red chilli powder, Tamarind, Turmeric
</Ingredients>
     <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

  <Product>
    <ID>17</ID>
    <Title>Jalfrezi</Title>
    <Thumbnail>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/thumb/Jalfrezi.jpg</Thumbnail>
    <BigImage>..//Web_App_Donato_Thesis/Images/iso/Jalfrezi.jpg</BigImage>
    <Description>A delicious chicken dish cooked in a thick creamy sauce. Best served with Basmati rice or Chappati’s. </Description>
    <Price>2.99 €</Price>
    <CookingDetails>1. In a cooking pan, sauté 50g of capsicum and 50g of onion (both cut into long strips) in 1 tbsp. (10g) of butter on a medium heat for 1 minute. Keep it aside.

2. Whisk the entire contents of this packet with 2 tbs. Of plain yoghurt and 250ml.of water in a bowl to form a smooth mixture.

3. In a frying pan, Sauté 250g of boneless chicken(small pieces) in 10g of butter until the chicken turns golden brown.

4. Add the mixture from the bowl and simmer on a low heat until the sauce becomes thick.

5. Add 50g of fresh single or double cream and bring to a boil. Add the sauted capsicum, onion and mix well.</CookingDetails>
    <Ingredients>Onion (43%), Refined Sunflower Oil (15%), Coriander Leaves (8.5%), Garlic (7.5%), Ginger (7.5%), Red Chilli Powder, Salt
, Mint Leaves, Spices, Turmer</Ingredients>
   <Origin>Pune, India</Origin>
    <TypeOfUser>Vegetarian, Vegan</TypeOfUser>
  </Product>

</Products>

